hi everybody this is nerdcon unlimit and
we're gonna talk about
massinger
c
has a life insurance or retirement a
second life
but we're gonna talk about the company
behind the creation of that commercial
the company name a new life financial
corporation is a canadian multinational
insurance company and financial services
provide headquarters in toronto ontario
canada
the company operates in canada and
nations on parsons united states
the insurance company manulife
japan created a commercial title
massinger kancho second life massinger
gold
to promote it is
mirai no tobai campaign
the video is about gonagi classic
massinger c robot filling the role of
the company section manager
now let's talk about the video
in the video
section manager massinger applied for
early retirement in his company by the
way using manulife
which become the lunchtime topic of his
co-workers their concern one of them it
is shocked by the news and considering a
singer as a hero for the company
yeah talk about a hero
they recount the various experience they
have with massinger which include having
drinks afterwards with him
now this is interesting part
a lot of the people in japan they has to
have some drinks or having a good time
with the bosses usually once a week and
especially on fridays regardless they
like it or not
not like here in united states i don't
like my boss as soon as i step out of
the door of the company i don't look
back
i don't want to know about my boss but
in japan
i hate my boss i can't stand my boss
well guess what you had to be with him
to make a human interaction in a matter
of way so during those stories the
experience with the manager under using
his photon bean and rose hurricane
attacks on other people they eventually
discussed that massinger has always
wanted to start a sova shop with his
wife
a superhero retired i never see that
anywhere before not even united states
but it's funny and by the way the wife
is not
not the character from the uh the anime
by the way this is a different one so i
don't know what happened to sayaka
back in time anyway so it is thanks to
my singers here arriving home to start
his second life an opening of the sofa
shop with his wife after retirement
really funny
i hope so you guys like it this is
nerdcon unlimit
see you soon
[Music]
foreign
okay
you